Guide to the Time Inc. Corporate Circulation Files 1940-1987 MS 3009-RG 50
New-York Historical Society
Time Inc. Corporate Circulation Records
1940-1987
New-York Historical Society
Time, inc.
MS 3009-RG 50
21.75 Linear feet in 22 record cartons and 2 flat folders
Corporate Circulation was a department of Time Inc. that supervised marketing of subscriptions for all of the company's magazines which included in-house creation of promotions as well as dealing with outside advertising agencies. The records consist of information on promotion efforts for specific magazines, information on magazine subscribers, and correspondence and agreements with foreign distributors.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are stored offsite and advance notice is required for use. Please contact manuscripts@nyhistory.org prior to your research visit to coordinate access. Keep in mind that it will take between two (2) and five (5) business days for collections to arrive, and you should plan your research accordingly.
Open to qualified researchers with the exception of restricted materials. Restricted materials include contracts. Restricted materials are located in box R86.
Arrangement
The materials within the Time Inc. Corporate Circulation Files record group are organized into three series: Series I. General Files; Series II. International Distribution Files; and Series III. Magazine Development Files.
Historical Note
Corporate Circulation was a department of Time Inc. that supervised marketing of subscriptions for all of the company's magazines which included in-house creation of promotions as well as dealing with outside advertising agencies. The department existed in two distinct periods; the first was from at least 1939 with P.I. (Pierrepont Isham) Prentice as Director from at least 1939 to 1942 and Francis Pratt serving in that role from at least 1944 to 1951, when the department was broken up to allow executives to concentrate their efforts on fewer magazines, or a single one, rather than having responsibility for all of them. This was purely a change in organizational structure with no positions eliminated so records continued to be produced by the same people with the same subject matter, which accounts for the presence in the collection of records post-dating the breakup of the unified Corporate Circulation department.
This reorganization was reversed in 1972 when the Corporate Circulation department was recreated to increase efficiency. The directorship was held by Kelso Sutton from 1972 to 1975, Ira R. "Ike" Slagter from 1975 to 1978, Lawrence Crutcher from 1978 to 1981, Christopher Meigher from 1981 to 1983, and, after a brief return by Crutcher in that year, Richard "Chip" Angle from 1983 to 1985. During Slagter's directorship some magazine concepts were studied and developed but ultimately never published. In 1985 the second incarnation of the department was divided again into two parts reporting to Chris Meigher and Bob Miller, respectively. The two parts ultimately worked underneath the umbrella of the Magazine Group.
The collection includes correspondence and contracts with foreign business entities to market and sell Time Inc. magazines abroad, many of which post-date the break-up of the first incarnation of Corporate Circulation. The most common correspondent on Time. Inc's side in these files is Vince Canavan, Credit Manager. It is likely that when the second incarnation of Corporate Circulation was created, it inherited these records.
Provenance
Gift of Time Inc. in 2015.
Related Materials
This finding aid relates to just one record group of the Time Inc. Records. For information about the other record groups and for overall information about the archives, please see the Guide to the Time Inc. Records (MS 3009). The Henry Luce Papers (MS 3014) were acquired with the Time Inc. Records. The collection of books acquired with the records are cataloged as the Time Inc. Reference Library.
The Time Inc. Advertising Promotion and Circulation Promotion Files (MS 3009-RG 21) contain similar information about promotion and marketing of Time Inc. magazines.
The majority of records regarding magazine development are in the Time Inc. Magazine Development Group Records (MS 3009-RG 40).
Scope and Contents
The collections consists of information on promotion efforts for specific magazines, including new magazines in development; samples of direct mailing promotions; correspondence including inter-office communications and letters from subscribers (complaints, etc.); budgets; information on magazine subscribers (subscription figures, rate of renewal, demographics, etc.); and correspondence and agreements with foreign distributors.
Advertising, Direct-mail -- Periodicals; Advertising, Magazine; Corporations -- History; Corporations -- New York (State) -- New York.; Corporation records; Organization files; Periodicals -- Circulation; Periodicals -- Publishing.; Publishers and publishing -- New York (State) -- New York.; Time, inc. -- Archives; Time, inc. -- History.; Time, inc. -- Management.
- Series I. General Files, 1940-1987; 19 Linear feet in 19 record cartons
  Scope and Contents
  1956 and Before consists of information on subscriptions such as new sales, renewals, and cancellations, monthly budget statements, and analysis of advertising efforts.
  1970 and Later contains samples of direct mail marketing tests done for Time Inc. magazines, studies and statistics on existing and potential subscribers to Time Inc. magazines regarding demographics and other information, information on outside advertising agencies employed by Time Inc., budgets, Audit Bureau of Circulation reports, correspondence and planning on marketing strategies and efforts, and material relating to substituting subscriptions of Life magazine for other magazines when the weekly edition of the former ceased publication in 1972.
  Arrangement
  Files are organized into two series reflecting the two distinct periods of this department: Subseries I.A. 1956 and Before; and Subseries I.B. 1970 and Later.
  - Subseries I.A. 1956 and Before, 1940-1956; 2 Linear feet in 2 record cartons
    Organized alphabetically.
    - Agent's Cage Renewals 1950-1951-1952 Study, 1950-1952 (Offsite-box 4060, Folder 1)
    - Agent's Cage Renewals 1953-1954 Study, by Types (Offsite-box 4060, Folder 2)
    - Analysis of Circular and Magazine Advertising Efforts and Tests, 1940-1948 (Offsite-box 4060, Folder 3)
    - Analysis of Circular and Magazine Advertising Efforts and Tests: Life: Christmas 1941-1947 (Offsite-box 4060, Folder 4)
    - Circulation: Life: 1949: Renewal Reports: Kill Class (Offsite-box 4060, Folder 5)
    - Circulation: Life: 1949: Renewal Reports: Kill Types (Offsite-box 4060, Folder 6)
    - Circulation: Life: 1949: Renewal Reports: Percentage (Offsite-box 4060, Folder 7)
    - Deferred Income: 1955, 1955-1956 (Offsite-box 4060, Folder 8)
    - Life: Cage Renewals, 1950-1956 (Offsite-box 4060, Folder 9)
    - Life: Deferred Commission, 1955 (Offsite-box 4060, Folder 10)
    - Life: Installment Sales Cancellations Percentage 1954-1955 (Offsite-box 4060, Folder 11)
    - Life Monthly Operating Statements: 1955 (Offsite-box 4061, Folder 1)
    - Life Monthly Operating Statements: 1956 (Offsite-box 4061, Folder 2)
    - Life Renewals 1942-47, 1956 (Offsite-box 4061, Folder 3)
    - Life- Time - Fortune Monthly Cage Receipts, 1951 (Offsite-box 4061, Folder 4-5)
    - Life- Time - Fortune Monthly Cage Receipts, 1953 (Offsite-box 4061, Folder 6-7)
    - O.T.C. & Coupon Receipts 1954 (Offsite-box 4061, Folder 8)
    - Publisher's Distribution Service (PDS), 1956 (Offsite-box 4061, Folder 9)
    - Renewal Meeting, 1956-1957 (Offsite-box 4061, Folder 10)
    - Renewal Reports - Add Percentage, 1949 (Offsite-box 4061, Folder 11)
    - Renewals - Life - Miscellaneous, 1953 (Offsite-box 4061, Folder 12)
    - Special Coupon Receipts 1952 (Offsite-box 4061, Folder 13)
    - Studies, 1950-1952 (Offsite-box 4061, Folder 14)
    - Studies, 1951-1952 (Offsite-box 4061, Folder 15)
  - Subseries I.B. 1970 and Later, 1970-1987; 17 Linear feet in 17 record cartons
    - 541 Fulfillment, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 4062, Folder 1-2)
    - AFP 1984 (Offsite-box 4062, Folder 3)
    - Ad Sales Postal Carrier Test 1984 (Offsite-box 4062, Folder 4)
    - Advo 1984 (Offsite-box 4062, Folder 5)
    - Agency, 1983-1986 (Offsite-box 4062, Folder 6)
    - Airlines, 1986 (Offsite-box 4062, Folder 7)
    - American Market Association (AMA) 1984-1985 (Offsite-box 4062, Folder 8)
    - Area of Dominant Influence (ADI) Reports 1983-1984 (Offsite-box 4062, Folder 9)
    - Attached Mail Test, 1985-1986 (Offsite-box 4062, Folder 10)
    - Bad Pay Screening 1983-1984 (Offsite-box 4062, Folder 11)
    - Billing 1985 (Offsite-box 4062, Folder 12)
    - Bloom, Silvia 1975-1976, 1980-1983 (Offsite-box 4062, Folder 13)
    - Broadcast, 1985-1986 (Offsite-box 4062, Folder 14)
    - Bruce A. Barnet (BAB) Personal, 1972-1974 (Offsite-box 4062, Folder 15)
    - Budget – 1987, September Estimate - 1986 (Offsite-box 4062, Folder 16-20)
    - Cable Contracts 1985 (Offsite-box 4062, Folder 17)
    - Cable Television Study 1984 (Offsite-box 4062, Folder 18)
    - Camera Month 1972 (Offsite-box 4062, Folder 19)
    - Camera Month Plans, 1972-1973 (Offsite-box 4062, Folder 20)
    - Camera Month: Direct Mail Lists, undated (Offsite-box 4063, Folder 1-2)
    - Camera Month: Returns: February 1972 (Offsite-box 4063, Folder 3)
    - Camera Monthly, 1972-1972 (Offsite-box 4063, Folder 4)
    - Campaign Summaries and Downloading, 1983 (Offsite-box 4063, Folder 5)
    - Carrier Route Data, 1983 (Offsite-box 4063, Folder 6)
    - Change of Address (COA), 1984 (Offsite-box 4063, Folder 7)
    - Change of Address (COA) Chicago Files, 1983-1984 (Offsite-box 4063, Folder 8)
    - Change of Address (COA): Christmas, 1983 (Offsite-box 4063, Folder 9)
    - Change of Address (COA) Student Mailings, 1984 (Offsite-box 4063, Folder 10)
    - Chicago Demographic Data, undated (Offsite-box 4063, Folder 11)
    - Chicago Monthly Status Reports, 1984 (Offsite-box 4063, Folder 12)
    - Chicago Planning, 1984 (Offsite-box 4063, Folder 13)
    - Chip Memos, 1984 (Offsite-box 4063, Folder 14)
    - Chip to Pat Memo Re: Meeting at Neodata [empty], undated (Offsite-box 4063, Folder 15)
    - Christmas 1984 (Offsite-box 4063, Folder 16)
    - Christmas Administration Follow-up 1985 (Offsite-box 4063, Folder 17)
    - Christmas Campaign: New Business, 1985 (Offsite-box 4063, Folder 18)
    - Christmas Promotion 1984 (Offsite-box 4063, Folder 19)
    - Circulation Director (CD) Objectives, 1984-1986 (Offsite-box 4063, Folder 20)
    - Circulation Division Strategic Plan 1983 (Offsite-box 4063, Folder 21)
    - Circulation Information Retrieval System (CIRS), 1983 (Offsite-box 4063, Folder 22)
    - Circulation Seminar, 1983 (Offsite-box 4063, Folder 23)
    - Class and Type Charts, 1982-1983 (Offsite-box 4063, Folder 24)
    - College Changes of Address (COAs), 1984 (Offsite-box 4063, Folder 25)
    - College Market, 1983-1984 (Offsite-box 4063, Folder 26)
    - College Market: General Research, 1984 (Offsite-box 4063, Folder 27)
    - Competitive Information, 1983 (Offsite-box 4063, Folder 28)
    - Compusearch Studies, undated (Offsite-box 4064, Folder 1)
    - Computer, 1983 (Offsite-box 4064, Folder 2)
    - Computer Mapping, undated (Offsite-box 4064, Folder 3)
    - Computer Usage, 1984 (Offsite-box 4064, Folder 4)
    - Comselect, 1983 (Offsite-box 4064, Folder 5)
    - Consumer Direct Inc., 1983 (Offsite-box 4064, Folder 6)
    - Control Data Bases, 1982 (Offsite-box 4064, Folder 7)
    - Corrections – Questions, 1983 (Offsite-box 4064, Folder 8)
    - Cover Test, 1984 (Offsite-box 4064, Folder 9)
    - Creative Automation, undated (Offsite-box 4064, Folder 10)
    - Current Magazine Development, 1985 (Offsite-box 4064, Folder 11-12)
    - Database Testing, 1984 (Offsite-box 4064, Folder 13)
    - Decoy/Salting Project, undated (Offsite-box 4064, Folder 14)
    - Delegates, 1984 (Offsite-box 4064, Folder 15)
    - Demographic Analysis, 1983 (Offsite-box 4064, Folder 16)
    - Demographic Data Census, 1981-1983 (Offsite-box 4064, Folder 17)
    - Demographic Facts- General, 1983 (Offsite-box 4064, Folder 18)
    - Demographic Institute 1983 (Offsite-box 4064, Folder 19)
    - Demographic Summary, 1983 (Offsite-box 4064, Folder 20)
    - Demographic Trends, 1983 (Offsite-box 4064, Folder 21)
    - Direct Mail Data Base, undated (Offsite-box 4064, Folder 22)
    - Direct Mail Promotion, 1983 (Offsite-box 4064, Folder 23)
    - Direct Mail Results, 1983 (Offsite-box 4064, Folder 24)
    - Direct Mail Schedules, 1984 (Offsite-box 4064, Folder 25)
    - Direct Mail Volumes: 1984 (Offsite-box 4064, Folder 26)
    - Direct Mail: Miscellaneous, 1983 (Offsite-box 4064, Folder 27)
    - Direct Mail Monthly Notes, 1983 (Offsite-box 4064, Folder 28)
    - Direct Mail/Bad Pay Screening, 1983 (Offsite-box 4064, Folder 29)
    - Direct Marketing Association (DMA) Conferences, 1983-1984 (Offsite-box 4064, Folder 30)
    - Direct Marketing Association (DMA) – Chicago – October 14-17, 1984 (Offsite-box 4064, Folder 31)
    - Direct Marketing Computer Association (DMCA), 1984 (Offsite-box 4064, Folder 32)
    - Direct Marketing Technology, 1984 (Offsite-box 4064, Folder 33)
    - Discover, 1985-1986 (Offsite-box 4064, Folder 34-35)
    - Discover, 1986 (Offsite-box 4065, Folder 1)
    - Discover, 1986 (Offsite-box 4065, Folder 2)
    - Discover: Budget 1987: Re-estimates: Operations Review 8/6/86, 1986 (Offsite-box 4065, Folder 3)
    - Discover/Science '86, 1986 (Offsite-box 4065, Folder 4)
    - DISSOS, 1984 (Offsite-box 4065, Folder 5)
    - Duplicate Elimination (Dupe-Elim) Test, 1983 (Offsite-box 4065, Folder 6)
    - Ecological Study, 1984 (Offsite-box 4065, Folder 7)
    - EDP Lists 1979/80 – Past, 1980 (Offsite-box 4065, Folder 8)
    - EDP Requests, 1983 (Offsite-box 4065, Folder 9)
    - Education Market, 1984 (Offsite-box 4065, Folder 10)
    - Employee Compensation, 1985 (Offsite-box 4065, Folder 11)
    - Expenses, 1969-1972 (Offsite-box 4065, Folder 12)
    - Fortune, 1985-1986 (Offsite-box 4065, Folder 13)
    - Fulfillment Reorganization, 1986 (Offsite-box 4065, Folder 14-15)
    - Jeremy Koch- Fortune, Home/Office Project, 1986 (Offsite-box 4065, Folder 16)
    - Legal, 1985-1986 (Offsite-box 4065, Folder 17)
    - Legal Guidelines, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 4065, Folder 18)
    - Leisure, 1985-1986 (Offsite-box 4065, Folder 19-20)
    - Letters Department (LD): Complaints January-June 1973 (Offsite-box 4066, Folder 1)
    - Letters Department (LD): Complaints July to August 1973 (Offsite-box 4066, Folder 2)
    - Letters Department (LD): Complaints, 1973 (Offsite-box 4066, Folder 3)
    - Letters Department (LD): Complaints - 1974 (Offsite-box 4066, Folder 4)
    - Letters Department (LD): Special Complaints - 1974 (Offsite-box 4066, Folder 5)
    - Letters Department (LD): Special Complaint Report, [1974] (Offsite-box 4066, Folder 6)
    - Life: 1970 Original Budget (Offsite-box 4066, Folder 7)
    - Life: 1972 Original Budget (Offsite-box 4066, Folder 8)
    - Life: 1973 Original Budget Expenses, 1972 (Offsite-box 4066, Folder 9)
    - Life: 1973 Original Budget Newsstand, 1972 (Offsite-box 4066, Folder 10)
    - Life: 1973 Original Budget, 1972 (Offsite-box 4066, Folder 11)
    - Life: 1973 Original Budget (Offsite-box 4066, Folder 12)
    - Life: 1973 Print Order (Offsite-box 4067, Folder 1)
    - Life: 1973 Promotion Budget (Offsite-box 4067, Folder 2)
    - Life, 1985-1987 (Offsite-box 4067, Folder 3)
    - Life: Audit Bureau of Circulation (ABC) 12/70, 1971 (Offsite-box 4067, Folder 4)
    - Life: Audit Bureau of Circulation (ABC) 6/71, 1971 (Offsite-box 4067, Folder 5)
    - Life: Audit Bureau of Circulation (ABC) Rules, 1972 (Offsite-box 4067, Folder 6)
    - Life: Audit Bureau of Circulation (ABC) Statements 6/30/70, 1970 (Offsite-box 4067, Folder 7)
    - Life: Audit Bureau of Circulation (ABC) Statement 12/31/69, 1969 (Offsite-box 4067, Folder 8)
    - Life: Audit Bureau of Circulation (ABC) Statement 12/31/71, 1971 (Offsite-box 4067, Folder 9)
    - Life: Audit Bureau of Circulation (ABC) Statements, 1961-1972 (Offsite-box 4067, Folder 10)
    - Life: Dissolution - Refunds and Invoices, 1973 (Offsite-box 4067, Folder 11-12)
    - Life: Dissolution – Substitution Information, 1972 (Offsite-box 4067, Folder 13)
    - Life: Futures, 1986 (Offsite-box 4067, Folder 14)
    - Life: Inventory, undated (Offsite-box 4067, Folder 15)
    - Life: Metro Mail, 1972, 1974 (Offsite-box 4067, Folder 16)
    - Life: November Re-estimate - 1986 (Offsite-box 4067, Folder 17)
    - Life: Publisher's Distribution Service (PDS) - Complaints, 1972-1973 (Offsite-box 4067, Folder 18)
    - Life: Print Order Model, 1972 (Offsite-box 4067, Folder 19)
    - Life: Print Order Summary, 1972 (Offsite-box 4067, Folder 20)
    - Life: Print Orders, 1972 (Offsite-box 4067, Folder 21)
    - Life: Print Orders, 1972 (Offsite-box 4067, Folder 22)
    - Life: Promotion, 1972 (Offsite-box 4067, Folder 23)
    - Life: Radio Promotion, 1972 (Offsite-box 4067, Folder 24)
    - Life: Rates, 1972 (Offsite-box 4067, Folder 25)
    - Life: Rate, 1972-1973 (Offsite-box 4067, Folder 26)
    - Life: Reference Material: New York Times 10-K Report, 1973 (Offsite-box 4067, Folder 27)
    - Life: Subscription Substitution Cards, undated (Offsite-box 4067, Folder 28)
    - Life: Weekly Estimate, 1972 (Offsite-box 4067, Folder 29)
    - Look Non-Respondents – Transferred to Life, 1972 (Offsite-box 4067, Folder 30)
    - Look Non-Respondents – Transferred to Time, 1972 (Offsite-box 4067, Folder 31)
    - Look Renewals, 1972 (Offsite-box 4067, Folder 32)
    - Magazine Demographics Research, 1985 (Offsite-box 4067, Folder 33)
    - Magazine Development, 1984-1986 (Offsite-box 4067, Folder 34)
    - Magazine Development, 1985 (Offsite-box 4068, Folder 1)
    - McKinsey Project, 1985 (Offsite-box 4068, Folder 2-3)
    - Monthly Receipts, 1986 (Offsite-box 4068, Folder 4)
    - National Demographics and Lifestyles (NDL), 1986 (Offsite-box 4068, Folder 5)
    - P&L Effect of Basic Rate Increases, 1974 (Offsite-box 4068, Folder 6)
    - Payment, 1971-1972 (Offsite-box 4068, Folder 7)
    - Picture Week, 1985-1986 (Offsite-box 4068, Folder 8-9)
    - Picture Week, 1985 (Offsite-box 4068, Folder 10-11)
    - Postal Rates, 1972 (Offsite-box 4068, Folder 12)
    - President's Luncheon Bi-Weekly Circulation Report, 1972 (Offsite-box 4068, Folder 13)
    - Promotion, 1986 (Offsite-box 4068, Folder 14)
    - Proposals and Strategic Plans, 1986 (Offsite-box 4068, Folder 15)
    - Publisher's Clearing House, 1972 (Offsite-box 4068, Folder 16)
    - Purchasing, 1986 (Offsite-box 4068, Folder 17)
    - Quality Direct Mail Costs and Results, 1985 (Offsite-box 4068, Folder 18-19)
    - Re-estimate June 1986 (Offsite-box 4068, Folder 20)
    - Re-estimate March 1986 (Offsite-box 4068, Folder 21)
    - Re-estimate, 1984-1985 (Offsite-box 4068, Folder 22)
    - Real Estate / Home Office, 1984-1986 (Offsite-box 4069, Folder 1)
    - Renewals, 1986 (Offsite-box 4069, Folder 2)
    - Renewals: 541 Memos: Miscellaneous Mail: Billing, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 4069, Folder 3)
    - Research, 1985 (Offsite-box 4069, Folder 4)
    - Research (continued) (1), 1985-1986 (Offsite-box 4069, Folder 5-6)
    - Research (continued) (2), 1986 (Offsite-box 4069, Folder 7-8)
    - Research Results, 1986 (Offsite-box 4069, Folder 9-10)
    - Science '86 Conversion, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 4069, Folder 11)
    - Sports Illustrated, 1986 (Offsite-box 4069, Folder 12-13)
    - Sports Illustrated: 1986 Christmas Campaign: Renewals, 1985-1987 (Offsite-box 4069, Folder 14)
    - Sports Illustrated: 1986 Christmas Television Campaign (Offsite-box 4069, Folder 15-17)
    - Sports Illustrated: 1986 Estimate Notebook: Year-End-Close June-November (Offsite-box 4070, Folder 1)
    - Sports Illustrated: Christmas 1986 Renewals (Offsite-box 4070, Folder 2-4)
    - Sports Illustrated: Christmas, 1985 (Offsite-box 4070, Folder 5-6)
    - Sports Illustrated: Christmas, 1985 (Offsite-box 4070, Folder 7-8)
    - Sports Illustrated: Circulation Campaigns, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 4070, Folder 9-10)
    - Sports Illustrated: Direct Mail Fall 1986 Panel 1: Control National (Offsite-box 4070, Folder 11)
    - Sports Illustrated: Direct Mail Fall 1986 Panel 2: Price: .99 vs. $2.25 (Offsite-box 4070, Folder 12)
    - Sports Illustrated: Direct Mail Fall 1986 Panel 3: 1.11 vs. $2.25 (Offsite-box 4070, Folder 13)
    - Sports Illustrated: Direct Mail Fall 1986 Panel 4: 1.13 vs. $2.25 (Offsite-box 4070, Folder 14)
    - Sports Illustrated: Direct Mail Fall 1986 Panel 5: 1.15 vs. 2.25 (Offsite-box 4070, Folder 15)
    - Sports Illustrated: Direct Mail Fall 1986 Panel 6: 1.17 vs. $2.25 (Offsite-box 4070, Folder 16)
    - Sports Illustrated: Direct Mail Fall 1986 Panel 7: 1.19 vs. $2.25 (Offsite-box 4070, Folder 17)
    - Sports Illustrated: Direct Mail Fall 1986 Panel 8: Offer: Risk Free (Control) (Offsite-box 4070, Folder 18)
    - Sports Illustrated: Direct Mail Fall 1986 Panel 9: Offer: Risk Free (Offsite-box 4070, Folder 19)
    - Sports Illustrated: Direct Mail Fall 1986 Panel 10: Offer: "Like Getting Issues Free" (Offsite-box 4070, Folder 20)
    - Sports Illustrated: Direct Mail Fall 1986 Panel 11: Early Reply-By Date (Offsite-box 4070, Folder 21)
    - Sports Illustrated: Direct Mail Fall 1986 Panel 12: Offer: "Give a Free Sub" (Offsite-box 4070, Folder 22)
    - Sports Illustrated: Direct Mail Fall 1986 Panel 13: Offer: Regionalized Edit (Offsite-box 4070, Folder 23)
    - Sports Illustrated: Direct Mail Fall 1986 Panel 14: Offer: Descending Term Option (Offsite-box 4070, Folder 24)
    - Sports Illustrated: Direct Mail Fall 1986 Panel 15: Offer: Credit Card (Offsite-box 4070, Folder 25)
    - Sports Illustrated: Direct Mail Fall 1986 Panel 16: Control (Premiums) (Offsite-box 4070, Folder 26)
    - Sports Illustrated: Direct Mail Fall 1986 Panel 17: Premium: Videocassette (Offsite-box 4070, Folder 27)
    - Sports Illustrated: Direct Mail Fall 1986 Panel 18: Premium: Video to Video Households [empty] (Offsite-box 4071, Folder 1)
    - Sports Illustrated: Direct Mail Fall 1986 Panel 29: Package Test: Instant Winner (Offsite-box 4071, Folder 2)
    - Sports Illustrated: Direct Mail Fall 1986 Panel 30: Package Test: 5 Free Gifts (Offsite-box 4071, Folder 3)
    - Sports Illustrated: Direct Mail Fall 1986 Panel 32: Package Test: Get the Feeling - Premium (Offsite-box 4071, Folder 4)
    - Sports Illustrated: Direct Mail Fall 1986 Panel 33: Package Test: Get the Feeing - No Premium (Offsite-box 4071, Folder 5)
    - Sports Illustrated: Direct Mail Fall 1986 Panel 34: Package Test: Madden (Offsite-box 4071, Folder 6)
    - Sports Illustrated: Direct Mail Fall 1986 Panel 35 [empty] (Offsite-box 4071, Folder 7)
    - Sports Illustrated: Direct Mail Fall 1986 Panel 36 (Offsite-box 4071, Folder 8)
    - Sports Illustrated: Direct Mail Fall 1986 Panel 36: Timing Test: July 18 (Offsite-box 4071, Folder 9)
    - Sports Illustrated: Direct Mail Fall 1986 Panel 37: Sweepstakes; Control Madden (Offsite-box 4071, Folder 10)
    - Sports Illustrated: Direct Mail Fall 1986 Panel 38 [empty] (Offsite-box 4071, Folder 11)
    - Sports Illustrated: Direct Mail Fall 1986 Panel 39: Sweepstakes: No Chit (Offsite-box 4071, Folder 12)
    - Sports Illustrated: Direct Mail Fall 1986 Panel 40: Sweepstakes: To Agent Sold Hold Lists (Offsite-box 4071, Folder 13)
    - Sports Illustrated: Direct Mail Fall 1986 Panel 41 [empty] (Offsite-box 4071, Folder 14)
    - Sports Illustrated: Direct Mail Fall 1986 Panel 42: Control: Regional Vid 2 (Offsite-box 4071, Folder 15)
    - Sports Illustrated: Direct Mail Fall 1986 Panel 43: Control (Offsite-box 4071, Folder 16)